oh wait Dantley where's the negative
name so you're looking for the opposite
here you're looking for it in there no
I'm not
that's what I see these are neutral
places these are positive negative
points so because they were work because
of these things they were your oxidizing
is sticking to upper and he Angie books
with audio one it's sticking to it there
this here is not working offices please
here is electroplated it's an officer
charged it's not as neutral it's an
opposite so this here is get sorting
through the could it be shortened
through them and what else the water
through the different kind of things but
you have different reactions and it's
creative working yeah this year is
taking them did you not see that that
college playing female stated I saw I do
that inside is that a months are the
fight to the other response positive
ones negative sure that come on Bobby
hill anyway we don't know we don't know
can't be stupid if you don't know we
don't see and you don't understand
that's not stupidity that's just funny
important to the right degree at the
right time do you know engineers yuri
two ladies that you're insulators are
actually
here in slightest maybe should see this
thing that's harder the insulator is
negative because it's plain yeah and
that's how I got it went to would be
filthy koobideh
find the right one one there look
usually a / - thank you
we say get the picture right did you
know claim it went to their other work
and the other one so I was just twisted
and this one went to a dirty one yeah
okay and this is you 31 thank can you
see it breaking again it's pulling two
pieces and sending a look and you're
looking at the magnetic field you're
looking a lexical field Mary have a look
to your electrical magnetic field look
where is it man blue team see look you
should know that there because you're
being trying to build a dee-nice coils
oh yeah and you don't get none up to
sell you're getting a looping around the
ends because that on the ends change the
field compared to us down the guns
and and this one we the seam up the guts
singe completely see you see that
centerfield over to that side so and
stop that from working on that side
because of the sink general there's no
will be if we've been acting like the
world because they say the same to the
complete over the side because the field
traveling sideways not up and down shuts
down completely across and do when you
got other ones sit around that's what
these are is traveling through each one
it's shutting down the only all yourself
so what you're ending up with is the
your oscilloscope will be a little beams
like what you've got in coils sitting
relaxed and then when you come up the
top there's your magnetic arc on the end
say 52 magnetic axe because I what's
happening these insulators is their
shorting out and then for every action
there is I they put equal and opposite
realize there is no final negative its
claim and there itself are positive it's
dirty oxidizing and pulling the pieces
so this L is just
to get your reaction you're doing no
more of the same reaction that you're
doing throw it all away use oil in
plates and throw anything in and
handfuls of foot and caustic cider and
electrolyte but put one doing any good
to run again right am i doing any good
for good gases or anything else all
right you can well with it you can watch
your home for a fire break and
everything else can we freak who is your
around set up merry video using
stainless which is a piss-poor conductor
but do you want conductivity now you
don't want to contact you because
conductivity is positive and Ely from
north and south or you understand when
you're getting that you see this you
know this is what security and these
things you know on this travel through
so it's done exactly the same in that
one the same Marcus our next one out and
you clean on the inside but you're
breaking beyond your insulators on the
air side that's what the marks are now
this is a negative side to a positive
together so negative touched onto their
clean but the other side a negative is
positive so one is touching they're all
the rest of it become positive with
earlier now the only other way where
pleasure school in the area
video tactic ensured still have it is
the office that occurred instead of
always securing he's insulated planet
draping black and blue marks into the
stainless dinner because he dodged
straight through to an opposite field
than any stuffed enough you just got
positive negative and all these field
effects are traveling up and down it
just goes through it went through and
through
okay keeps going around repeat fix it
setting up the wrong field is that
terrible did you happen tonight
did you know you stack them that way do
you clean dirty so you feel now went
this way where this one here is going in
and out see it's going that one so your
magnetic fields are changing positions
because now this outside one is the
outside one is completely changed
because what's happened is is each
running up and down it's not in the
middle looking to look that's a complete
face
he said not oxidized and it won't come
off some minerals or something when I
pull the pieces putted atomically into
the water then electroplated it
completely onto the flipping theater
whoa cut off there you can see that but
you got a bugger it well you'll never
change the field effect by standing it
did you stuff up the stands
okay but this one here is setting it up
between a weld in the bottom which is
down there and it's pulling it to pieces
if you look at the black down there when
you threw this on all this will
come to the surface all this brown crap
and everything it's got to keep pulling
out the pieces to the next hundred years
I'm here to stop that home from planting
water in both sided design over the
backpacks the lifting wrong stuff each
conductor you know figure this rock and
then what you got is that sale from
medium is no mayor is an opposite charge
where you've got these sideways this is
nothing in the middle a native virtually
in that Center in positive 5 and
positive down and positive shortly out
there computer don't even say okay any
other later electric whining play game
changer hello another crime on that
magnet anything economics winters were
here when I didn't do what was fine with
magnetic I'll tell you they had to get
right before they did that and then I
put it into a barrel of water with your
riders under electricity and everything
else
bastards apart he is he's gotta get
there girl are you log eat it you know
Tori either that thing they see you too
fast you want your help if you don't
learn to look at no hair you're not
willing to look at what you've done
he why feel that if you don't know he'll
make me a few runs I'll even build up
but only built the Phil bit very good
Betty if you and your father or whatever
else he's he's your father did I used to
get a whoopee in here and work of it now
I should get together because what you
were doing one way